A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Director of the Virginia Council on the Environment, 1970-1988
Library of Virginia
- Series V: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 30902], 1971-1980., Extent: 21 cu. ft. (21 boxes). (Box 1-21)
  - Permit Coordination Task Force, Virginia Marine Resources Commission and the State Water Control Board, Joint permit, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Permit Coordination Task Force, Background information, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Permit Coordination Task Force, Committee on current process, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - State Chamber of Commerce, Air Quality Standards Committee, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Agribusiness Council, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Forestry Association, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - EPA, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Dept. of Transportation, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Dept. of Transportation, Federal Aviation Administration, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Dept. of Agriculture and Commerce, Correspondence, 1970-1978 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Air Pollution Control Board, Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Dept. of Conservation and Economic Development, 1971-1976 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Dept. of Conservation and Economic Development, Division of Parks, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Dept. of Conservation and Economic Development, Division of Water Resources, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Erosion and Sedimentation, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - State Energy Office, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - State Energy Office, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - State Energy Office, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - State Energy Office, Conference, 1974 November (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Coastal Study Commission, CRM program, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Coastal Study Commission, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 18-19)
  - Virginia Coastal Study Commission, Meeting, 1977 April (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Virginia Coastal Study Commission, Meeting, 1976 June (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, 1976-1979 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1978 December (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1978 September (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1978 June (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Conference, 1978 April (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1978 March (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, Exemptions Sub-Committee, 1978 March (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1978 January (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1977 December (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1977 November (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, Exemptions Committee, 1977 October (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1977 August (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1977 April (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1977 March (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1977 January (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1976 August (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Proposed interim procedures (for implementation of the multiple permit process), Mailing list, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Proposed interim procedures (for implementation of the multiple permit process), Clippings, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Proposed interim procedures (for implementation of the multiple permit process), Notices, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Proposed interim procedures (for implementation of the multiple permit process), Staff report, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Proposed interim procedures (for implementation of the multiple permit process), Memos, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 5-6)
  - Proposed interim procedures (for implementation of the multiple permit process), Staff proposal, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Garden Club of Virginia, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 8-9)
  - Float Fisherman of Virginia, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Coastal Plains Regional Commission, Environmental Affairs Advisory Committee, 1974-1979 (Box 14, Folder 11-14)
  - Virginia Wildlife Federation, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Federation of Women's Clubs, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - EPA, Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - State Chamber of Commerce, 1973-1977 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Conservation Council of Virginia, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - RLEP (Rappahannock League for Environmental Protection, Inc.), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Piedmont Environmental Council, 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - League of Women Voters of Virginia, 1974-1976 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Water Control Board, Souther River Watershed Flood Plain Project, 1972-1976 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Water Control Board, 1974-1978 (Box 14, Folder 24-26)
  - Health issues correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 14, Folder 27-30)
  - Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries, Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Technical Advisory Task Force, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Highway Department, Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Industrial Development, Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - VPI (Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University), Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Regional organizations, Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Virginia Outdoor's Foundation, Correspondence, 1971-1979 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - VIMS (Virginia Institute of Marine Science), Correspondence, 1970-1978 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Soil and Water Conservation Commission, Correspondence, 1971-1978 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Commission of Outdoor Recreation, Correspondence, 1970-1978 (Box 14, Folder 40-41)
  - Office of Special Programs, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Marine Resources Commission, Correspondence, 1970-1977 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Permit Coordination Task Force, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 1-7)
  - Environmental Impact Statement process, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Impact Statement, Council on the Environment's role, 1971-1973 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Council on Environmental Quality, NEPA (National Environmental Policy Act) Hearing Questionnaire, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 10-12)
  - Environmental Impact Statement, Procedures and training, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Procedures manual and guidelines for the Environmental Impact Statement Program in the Commonwealth of Virginia, Original and copy, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Tidewater Interagency Committee on Permissible Water Uses, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, York Chapter, Inc., Workshops, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Coastal Zone Management, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - CRM (Coastal Resources Management) - BLM (Bureau of Land Management), Meeting, 1976 August (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - CRM (Coastal Resources Management) Committee, Meeting, 1976 August (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Coastal Zone Management, Meeting, 1976 October (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - CRM (Coastal Resources Management) Committee, Meeting, 1976 October (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - CRM (Coastal Resources Management) Committee, Meeting, 1976 December (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - CRM (Coastal Resources Management) Committee, Issue papers and comments on program alternatives, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 23-24)
  - CRM (Coastal Resources Management) Committee, Meeting, 1977 April (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - CRM (Coastal Resources Management) Committee, Meeting, 1977 June (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - CRM (Coastal Resources Management) Committee, Workshop, 1977 June (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - CRM (Coastal Resources Management) Committee, Meeting, 1977 July (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - CRM (Coastal Resources Management) Committee, Press release and newsletter, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - CRM (Coastal Resources Management) Committee, Meeting, 1977 October (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - CRM (Coastal Resources Management) Committee, Meeting, 1977 December (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - CRM (Coastal Resources Management) Committee, Meeting, 1978 January (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Coastal Study Commission, Meeting, 1978 January (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - CRM (Coastal Resources Management) Committee, Grant applications, 1978 March (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Permit Coordination Task Force, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Reference materials, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Appropriation requests, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 16, Folder 4-9)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Policies and procedures, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Preliminary program structure, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Refence, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Analysis, 1976-1980 (Box 16, Folder 13-14)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Report, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Original report and mailing list, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Recommendations vs. Programs, 1976-178 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Worksheets, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Notes, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Financial summaries, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Budget program, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Dept. of Agriculture and Commerce, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, State Air Pollution Control Board, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 23-24)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Commission on Outdoor Recreation, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Dept. of Conservation and Economic Development, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Work charts, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Council on the Environment, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Council on the Environment, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Dept. of Health, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 31-32)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Historic Landmarks Commission, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Marine Resources Commission, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Soil and Water Conservation Commission, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, State Water Control Board, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Virginia Institute of Marine Science, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Program budgeting, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Council on the Environment, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, State Air Pollution Control Board, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Commission on Outdoor Recreation, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Marine Resources Commission, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Soil and Water Conservation Commission, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Agency funding summary, Program breakdown, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Agency crosswalks, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Environmental agencies, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Joint Environmental Agencies' Budget, Schedule for activities, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Shellfish vs. Development, 1975-1977 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1978 January-July (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Federal Regional Council meeting, 1978 October (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Council on Transportation, 1977 November (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Council on Transportation meeting, 1977 September (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Council on Transportation meeting, 1977 August (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Council on Transportation meeting, 1977 July (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Council on Transportation, 1977 March (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Governor's Council on Transportation meeting, 1976 November (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Governor's Council on Transportation meeting, 1976 October (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Governor's Council on Transportation meeting, 1976 September (Box 17, Folder 12-13)
  - Governor's Council on Transportation meeting, 1976 July (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Governor's Council on Transportation meeting, 1976 May (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Governor's Council on Transportation meeting, Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Land Use Council, Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Land Use Council, Organization of, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Land Use Council, Background information, 1971-1975 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Land Use Council, Key Facilities Committee, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 20-21)
  - Land Use Council, DGLS Study, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 22-23)
  - Land Use Council, Growth Policies Commission, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Land Use Council, Meeting, 1974 October (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Land Use Council, Meeting, 1974 December (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Land Use Council, Meeting, 1975 March (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Land Use Council, Meeting, 1975 April (Box 17, Folder 28-29)
  - Land Use Council, Key Facilities Committee meeting, 1975 August (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Land Use Council, Meeting, 1975 September (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Land Use Council, Meeting, 1976 August (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Land Use Council, Meeting, 1976 November (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Land Use Council, Meeting, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Land Use Council, Meeting, 1977 May (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Land Use Council, Meeting, 1977 August (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Land Use Council, Southern Conference Meeting, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Land Use Council, Legislative Issues and Options Conference, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Land Use Council, Realtors Institute Conference, 1975 July (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Land Use Council, Virginia Airport Land Use Planning seminar, 1978 August (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Land Use Council, Application correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Land Use Council, Study, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Land Use Council, Land issues and problems seminar, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 43-44)
  - Land Use Council, Rockingham County correspondence, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - SCC (State Corporation Commission), Application No. 71 VEPCO, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - SCC (State Corporation Commission), Notices about transmission lines, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 2-3)
  - SCC (State Corporation Commission), Application Nos. 19, 32-36 VEPCO, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - SCC (State Corporation Commission), Application for Certification from Potomac Edison, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - SCC (State Corporation Commission), Application for Certification from Jackson's Ferry-Axton line, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - SCC (State Corporation Commission), Application No. 100 VEPCO, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - SCC (State Corporation Commission), Application No. 39, 43, 49, 53, 54, 56 VEPCO, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - SCC (State Corporation Commission), Application for Certification from Appalachian Power Co., 1974 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - SCC (State Corporation Commission), Application No. 62-64 VEPCO, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Environmental Industry Conference, 1977 February (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Dept. of Highways and Transportation, Trail review of highway projects, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Analysis of options for implementing a vehicle inspection-maintenance program, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Wehner, Harrison, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Permit Coordination Task Force, Preliminary draft report, 1976 November (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Permit Coordination Task Force, First draft of booklet on Virginia's Environmental Regulatory Process 1974-1977 (Box 18, Folder 16-18)
  - Permit Coordination Task Force, Report, 1977 January (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Budget request, 1974-1976 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Budget request, 1976-1978 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Report covering achievements of Council on the Environment, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Budget with 5% reduction, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Budget requests, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Budget requests, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Budget requests, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Budget expenditure reduction request, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Allotment and appropriation transfers, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Statement of appropriations, expenditures, and balance, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Budget expenditure reduction request, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Budget expenditure reduction request, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Budget with 2 1/2 % reduction, 1976-1978 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Annual reports, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Annual reports, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Annual reports, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 3-10)
  - Annual reports, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 11-18)
  - Annual reports, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Annual report, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - IMPACT, Council on the Environment's Newsletter, Procedures and general information, 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 21-22)
  - IMPACT, Council on the Environment's Newsletter, 1976 October (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - IMPACT, Council on the Environment's Newsletter, 1976 July (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - IMPACT, Council on the Environment's Newsletter, 1975 November (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - IMPACT, Council on the Environment's Newsletter, 1975 September (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - IMPACT, Council on the Environment's Newsletter, 1975 May (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - IMPACT, Council on the Environment's Newsletter, 1975 March (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - IMPACT, Council on the Environment's Newsletter 1975 January (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Misc., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 1-5)
  - Science Museum of Virginia, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Interns, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 7-8)
  - Multiple permit coordinate, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Commission on state governmental management, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Employee training programs, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Monthly activity report, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Workshop on Behavioral theories, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Dept. of Rehabilitative Services, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Process Act, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Disclosure of economic interests of public officials, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Budget information, 1975-1978 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Misc., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Senate Joint Resolution No. 96, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Work plan, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Work plan, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Work plan, 1974-1977 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Work plan, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Work plan, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - EPA meeting, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Kepone Task Force, Minutes and agenda, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Kepone Task Force, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Kepone Task Force, Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Kepone Task Force, Meeting, 1978 January (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Assateague Island meeting, 1974 February (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Annual report, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 21-23)
  - Annual report, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 24-25)
  - Newsletter of the Council on the Environment, IMPACT, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Newsletter of the Council on the Environment, IMPACT, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Newsletter of the Council on the Environment, IMPACT, Drafts, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Newsletter of the Council on the Environment, IMPACT, Drafts, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Newsletter of the Council on the Environment, Digest of Environmental News, 1978 July (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Newsletter of the Council on the Environment, Digest of Environmental News, 1978 August (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Newsletter of the Council on the Environment, Digest of Environmental News, 1978 September (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Newsletter of the Council on the Environment, Digest of Environmental News, 1978 October (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Virginia's Environment, Brochure, Drafts, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 34-35)
- Series VI: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 32359], 1971-1979., Extent: 6 cu. ft. (6 boxes). (Box 1-6)
  - Federal Environmental Impact Statements
    - CAS [Civil Aeronautices Board], Capacity Reduction Agreement, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - NASA [National Aeronautics and Space Administration], Refuse Fired Steam Generating Facility, Langley Research Center, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
    - NASA [National Aeronautics and Space Administration], National Transonic Facility, Langley Research Center, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], ASC [Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service], Agriculture Conservation Program, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], ASC [Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service], emergency Conservation Measures Program, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], ASC [Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service], Rural Environmental Conservation Program, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], ASC [Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service], Rural Environmental Conservation Program, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], ASC [Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service], Rural Environmental Assistance Program, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], FS [Forest Service], George Washington National Forest, Big Levels Unit, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], FS [Forest Service], Element Outline, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], FS [Forest Service], Fall Cankerworm Suppression, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], FS [Forest Service], Forestry Incentives Program, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], FS [Forest Service], Gypsy Moth Program, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], FS [Forest Service], Massanutten Mountain Land Use Plan, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], FS [Forest Service], George Washington and Monongahela National Forests, Laurel Fork Unit Plan, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], FS [Forest Service], George Washington National Forest, Lower Jackson River Unit #1, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], FS [Forest Service], George Washington National Forest, Massanutten Unit Plan, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], FS [Forest Service], Mount Rogers National Recreational Area and Scenic Highway, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], FS [Forest Service], George Washington National Forest, North River Unit, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 23-25)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], FS [Forest Service], George Washington National Forest, Piney River Unit, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 26-27)